<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: web | LMC Technology blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://lmc-eu.github.com/technology//blog/categories/web/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://lmc-eu.github.com/technology//"/>
  <updated>2013-02-19T09:38:23+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://lmc-eu.github.com/technology//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[LMC s.r.o.]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swiffy For SWF Banners Help]]></title>
    <link href="http://lmc-eu.github.com/technology//blog/2013/02/19/swiffy-for-swf-banners-help/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-19T10:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://lmc-eu.github.com/technology//blog/2013/02/19/swiffy-for-swf-banners-help</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I've prepared this presentation for purposes of our company and it describes benefits of utilizing <a href="https://www.google.com/doubleclick/studio/swiffy/">Swiffy</a> conversion tool for our/client banner ads business.
Our creative guys are great when using <em>Adobe Flash Professional</em> authoring tool and our customers love it, but <strong>growing iOS devices market share</strong> is already forcing us to change our current technology approach. This presentation should help us with the transformation process.</p>

<p>New <a href="https://github.com/paulrouget/dzslides">DZSlides</a> version, which I've used as the presentation engine, is a little bit less MSIE 9 friendly then its previous releases and I had to hack it a bit. So now the presentation works well in MSIE 10, Firefox, Chrome, Safari, Opera and acceptably also on MSIE 9 as well, but sorry, MSIE 8- ...
In the presentation slides is purposefully <strong>embedded SWF file</strong> and to have it <em>visible in Gecko browsers</em>, there is a trick, which must be used - add <strong>wmode="opaque"</strong> to the Flash object tag declaration; maybe will this hint save you some time, well, it cost me a lot to discover this, to be honest...</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="/assets/swiffy.html">Presentation Itself</a> which contains a lot of information for you to know how <em>(and if)</em> start to think differently, about how to serve/use your <em>Adobe-Fixed-Creatives</em> banner content</li>
<li><a href="/assets/banner.htm">Simple Banner Fallback Example</a> shows easiest possible markup for you to test proposed fallback scenario <em>(yes. MSIE 8 users, this is the only sensible link for you there...)</em></li>
<li><a href="http://svg.kvalitne.cz/swiffy/gallery.html">Sample Conversion Gallery</a> is collection of <em>(mostly)</em> LMC banners with positive results of Swiffy conversion process, with some comments, file size comparisons etc. <em>(those demos do not have proposed fallback applied to them so SVG aware browser is a must!)</em> Gallery is temporarily hosted on different server, because of some special mime type handling.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
